What's up, YouTube?
>> Hi guys. What's up, YouTube?
>> We're back. We back with another banger.
Get ready with us. Back. So, get ready
with us4.
It's currently
It's currently, let me check. Let me
check. Let me check.
>> Let me let me let me
>> 3:48.
So guys, me 3 in there,
but it's already the next day. It's on a
Saturday this Sunday. Saturday. Hey,
Sunday. Sunday. 3:48 p.m. So guys, we're
here traveling as a family.
>> Hi guys.
Say hi.
>> Hi guys. So guys um let's
let's
get ready. We're going to get
then from we catch our train which
we're supposed to be at the train
station
>> by by 8 but you're going to go earlier.
We're going to go earlier you keep
quiet. You're going to go earlier
because
>> I wish you
going to go earlier cuz we have to check
in the bags. will make sure everyone's
safety is at the top notch. So guys,
I'll show you my feet. I'm just wearing
my simple clothes and
jacket and don't mind. Guess where we
going to go? Guess
where we are going to be traveling.
Maybe locally, maybe internationally.
Tell me in the comment section. So
Get ready.
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. [laughter]
That's all I can say for now.
What's wrong?
tower is enough to go. Yeah, it's
currently 34 350
already. Yeah. So, let's go and get
ready. We're going to see each other
later. Bye-bye. So,
what do you mean?
>> We out and about. See you on the next.
Bye. So,
see you on the other side.
Good morning. We have left Nairobi
termin.
Guys,
Finally,
Exit.
Hello.
Well, you need to be
Knock knock
from there.
together.
Work pretty well.
Adventuring new things.
Imagining me waking up every morning.
Electronics.
Nice and clean.
That is my dining room over there.
Imagine
breakfast.
Look at the view behind a view. Look at
the view.
too much.
Good morning.
>> Oh yeah,
we have the balcony.
See the balcony. See the view. See the
see the ambient video of me. Look at the
view. Look at the view. Look at the
view. Is it giving? I love the view over
here, guys. Where is Ma, guys? Look at
the
>> Look at the view, guys.
>> See the sea. Look at the
>> I didn't see.
>> Wow.
>> Guys, look at the view in Mumb.
Yeah. So, that's the surprise part.
Let's go. Let's
move to the next part.
Look, I have this mirror. We have the TV
over here.
We have the TV, the Wi-Fi,
whatever.
>> Don't drop it. Don't open. Isn't
the name?
This is the boys bedroom.
>> So guys, that's the boys bedroom.
There's a special washroom over there.
But the boys, I didn't ask them for
permission.
From there we have
>> from there we have my bedroom. Okay.
>> Look the way it is.
Look that is where I'm going to be
spending my night for the past for the
next few um I don't know. You have a
over here,
a special tub that removes water,
>> and the camera,
>> the toilet,
>> the showering area,
>> and
yeah, we have special wardro
special
for me. Imagine.
>> Thank you. Enough.
>> Come, come, come.
>> It's enough.
>> Come.
Guys, this is the last.
This is the balcony.
Look at the view. Look at the area.
>> Wait,
let's one.
>> Hi.
>> Finish with you. We have the bathroom.
>> We have the bathtub.
[laughter] Look at the bathtub over
here. Look at the bathtub. We have the
toilet. Two special sinks. We have
bathing area. The shower gel over there.
We have mister ora.
We have a
hi.
So guys, thank you for staying with me
guys.
It's hot over here. It's day two in
Nevada.
I'll show you what my day looks like.
Yeah. So, come with me.
We go have breakfast. I step out to
wild. [screaming]
See the view. See the view. See the
view. See the view. You see the view
>> video the ambience.
This is the day.
This is my bag for the day.
>> Costume. Guys,
the other side.
No,
bye-bye.
Who's that talking?
>> Where are we going to
>> mall?
>> Mall to do what?
>> Shopping.
after eating.
>> Silver
just taking a whack.
Yeah.
I walk
means of transport
means of transport. We are going to walk
and it's my 17th
Come, come.
Hi guys.
Let me show you.
Let's come walk.
I need to burn down some fat. You get
it? I need to burn down some energy,
some calories. Yeah. But
anything
fit.
Yeah.
So
we
continue walking.
Time is money. Time is really money.
Time is money. You get it. Forget about
it.